pulsetv.com 2010-06-24

# Privacy - Pulse Direct, Inc.

> > Our pledge to you, our customer 
> 
> PulseTV.com respects your privacy. Our Internet site is meant to be a service to you. In order to provide you with the best products, timely information and quality customer service, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 
> 
> Your personal information: what we collect and how we use it: 
> 
> When you enter personal information in to the Shopping Cart, we collect your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card information. First, we use this information to fulfill your order and to communicate with you about your order. In fulfilling your order, we share your personal information with outside parties to the extent necessary to fulfill your order. In addition, 
> 
>   1. Our First Use of the Shopping Cart at PulseTV.com - We use the information you provide to: automatically place you on our e-mail list to receive special offers and updates about products and services, unless you edit your subscription profile at the time your order is placed; and make lists of our customers' names and postal addresses (but not e-mail addresses or phone numbers) available to pre-screened companies who have specific direct mail (e.g. catalog) product or service offers that we think may be of interest to you.
>   2. Your Subsequent Use of the Shopping Cart at PulseTV.com - If you have purchased a product from a PulseTV.com company before, unless you edit your subscription profile at the time your order is confirmed, your subscription status will remain unchanged.
> 

> 
> Whether you are using the Shopping Cart for the first time or not, if you later decide that you want to be removed from a list or do not want us to share your name and postal address information, simply unsubscribe from any message you recieve (unsubscribe links are always at the bottom of an email) 
> 
> When you send a gift and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's name and postal address. We use this information only to ship the product and confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to fulfill that order. 
> 
> When you enter a sweepstakes sponsored by PulseTV.com, we may ask for any or all of the following information: your name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number. Check the official rules or the actual sweepstakes for what information is requested for any individual sweepstakes. Unless the official rules for a particular sweepstakes provide otherwise, when you provide your e-mail address you will be signed up for PulseTV.com Companies e-mail newsletters and, if you provide us with your postal address, you will be added to our direct mail/catalog list. You can unsubscribe from the e-mail newsletters and/or direct mail/catalog list at any time by following the instructions in any message you recieve. 
> 
> Information about customers and visitors shared with third parties: 
> 
> As described in the section "When you enter personal information into the Shopping Cart", in addition to being placed on our e-mail newsletter list and direct mail/catalog list, we may make your name and postal address available to pre-screened companies who have specific direct mail (e.g. catalog) product or service offers that we think may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to share your name and postal address information, simply follow the instructions in any message you recieve. We also share information about our customers and visitors with trusted service providers who provide PulseTV.com with specific services and/or administer activities offered on the PulseTV.com site. (For example, we may provide customer information to companies that analyze our clickstream data in order to help us better design our site.) We also may use non-identifying and aggregate information (as opposed to identifiable individual information) about our customers and/or visitors to better design our website and we may provide it to advertisers and other third parties. 
> 
> Upon completing your purchase, we may present offers on behalf of third party partners on the order confirmation page. If you click on some of these promotional links and accept the offer(s), we will send your personal information to this party to complete the transaction. We do not share this information without your consent. 
> 
> On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law to do so, or protect the rights, property, or safety of PulseTV.com, our users, or others. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes. 
> 
> Requests to be unsubscribed will be processed immediately, however you may receive additional newsletters for up to 1 week. Delays may occur if the email address or postal address information you provide us does not match the information in our database. 
> 
> **Links to/from Other Sites**  
>  To enhance your shopping experience, the PulseTV.com site may have links to other sites on the Internet that are owned by third party vendors and other third parties (External Sites), or you may come to PulseTV.com from a link from an External Site. These other web sites will have their own rules on privacy that you should review. PulseTV.com is not responsible for the privacy policies of External Sites. 
> 
> **Cookies**  
>  PulseTV.com uses a feature of your Internet Web browser called a cookie to assign an identification code to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you. Cookies do not provide us with access to any credit card information. 
> 
> **Third Party Cookies**  
>  In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 
> 
> **Our Commitment to Data Security**  
>  To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 
> 
> **Notice of Changes**  
>  PulseTV.com’s Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice. At any time, you may visit our website to view the current policy.
